Dance! Dance! Drink! Enjoy!
Don't be shy now!
No flesh to weigh me down.
I mean, not that I had any to begin with.
Skeleton choke.
I'd call myself vain,
but I ain't got them.
Whatever, time to search.
this door smells fishy or rather it
would if I had enough yes three in a row
Oh, that's peculiar.
What are these dolls?
Huh?
No way!
A polygraph?
One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Set and sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're close to
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead on new horizons.
In view, shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top.
Fire!
We've lost connection!
Switch to another camera then! Hurry!
Damn it.
No way!
They made it past our fight on the
fence, but I'm heading up the falls now!
Go!
How are these fish climbing the waterfall?
That's lickety-slick.
Impressive.
Morons!
What the hell are you even doing?
Don't let that hag set
foot on the island. Go!
We have no protection set up once
they clear the water, though, sir.
And to be fair, we're dealing
with some very strong enemies.
We need a lot more time to set up weapons
to take down guys of their caliber.
Stop panicking.
Commander!
Lin-Lin can go to hell.
And she can take her family
with her at that, dammit.
You all need to get your shit together.
Now, prepare for an Alto war!
Let's not be complacent, shall we?
One ship, their
incompetence is astounding.
I'll end this.
We're nearing the top!
It looks like we'll make it up!
Oh, kind of!
I'm here!
Something's approaching!
I see that! Is it King?
Deronatan!
Open fire off!
Lickety-splitting already?
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
We're almost to the land of Wano!
Your time is up, Straw Hat.
She's coming back for more!
This might get ugly!
Oh, no!
You little bastard!
I won't let you enter our country.
Enjoy your watery grave, hag.
Hey, you're keeping up!
I'm trying, but why are we
running away in the first place?
They're after Sangoro, not us two!
Did you already forget that you knocked
out one of those Kyoshiro clowns too?
They're going to be looking for you!
Oh, my bad. Pass.
Look, we can't afford to
make Orochi angry right now.
The Tobiropo are the big
dogs and the beast pirates.
So we messed up bad if
they sent them after us.
An enemy! Time to bail!
It's just you two.
Don't scare me like that.
It's not safe here. Follow me. Right.
We're in some deep crap here.
There's no use in pointing fingers.
We can still salvage the mission,
but the element of surprise is the
only thing that's keeping us alive.
If they find out who we are, your
whole crew's as good as dead.
Damn.
That means Nami and Robin are in danger.
Make this one promise to me.
If you're captured, don't say a word
about the Kozuki Clan's involvement.
20 years of vengeance is on the line.
You have to swear to me, even
if they detain and torture you.
You can't mention the samurai
or the minks. You got that?
Keep your mouth shut
and let them kill you.
Loopy would never say something
like that. I'm not him.
So if we hide our faces,
can we still throw down?
Here, check this out.
I'm just an anonymous ass-kicker now!
We should avoid all confrontation.
I don't remember voting
you in as our captain.
You better hope I'm not caught.
Cause I'll spill
everything to save myself!
Not on my watch, you won't!
I'm gonna protect you so hard!
It worked!
Seriously?
A lady!
What caused that?
It must be the enemy!
We have nothing to do with this!
That's our family business!
We're unaffiliated with the
man you're in search of!
You just destroyed our livelihood!
With that, it will be
kicked out of the capital!
You want to hold it against someone?
Then blame it on Sangoro.
Where are the other Sabo shops?
I'll destroy every last
one until I find them!
Bring me the fool who dared to
mess with the Kyoshiro clan!
I'm brewing your patience.
I might just have to eat you!
Sangoro!
Sangoro! Hey!
Please, come out!
Sangoro!
Show yourself!
What a shame.
It seems like he's too
much of a coward to man up.
I'm in the mood for dessert now.
They want to lure you out. Ignore them.
Our only priority is getting out safe.
No.
I have to help them.
Wait, Sanchi, come back!
Stop!
We have nothing to do with Batman!
Then find him for me!
Bring me Sandoron, the Sabo cook!
Looking for me? Huh?
I'm right here!
Diablo, Jamba!
Konkisei!
He came out!
That's the guy, Scar
with the special Sabo!
So there you are!
I've been looking for you,
what took you so long?
Page one, reporting in.
Found the target, sixth
block, district two, right?
Roger, that we'll send in some backup!
Hehehehe. Excellent.
You prepared to meet your end?
You got dinosaur powers, huh?
You asshole!
Sangoro! Come on! Time to go!
If Drake and Hawkins show
up, then everything is over.
I know.
but luckily this bastard
doesn't know who I am.
I won't get injured and
I'll stay undercover.
i just have to beat him
in an instant right.
recruiting allies is important of course.
but having fewer enemies is good too.
You're gonna back up those
big words you're using.
guys go on without me!
I promise they won't find out.
My identity will remain a secret.
That cook guy really came out of hiding?
What the hell?
Does he have a death wish?
Well, what do you know?
I found a use for this thing. Huh?
What is that?
A can of food?
Now, don't go getting
the wrong idea about me.
Just because I'm trying this
doesn't mean I'm like them.
I'm willing to give this a shot, though.
Why do you insist on
making things difficult?
So what do you think
Sangoro has planned, huh?
We're fighting an emperor of the sea.
There are going to be times
when we can't save a life,
especially if we're too stubborn.
But if I swallow my pride, then there
are people I can save right here and now.
I'm tired of hearing you kill you!
If this has the power to help,
then I clearly need to use it.
Well, here goes.
You really like wasting
my time, don't you?
What's changing your
clothes supposed to do?
Black leg.
Ugh!
That costume!
Like a superhero! Wow!
So cool!
How's that thing work?
Hold up. Seriously?
I recognize that outfit.
That can't be right, can it?
That's from Saru, Warrior of the Sea.
He's wearing one of
the villain's costumes.
Actually, it's all coming back to me now.
That's the third member of the army of
evil, Germa Double Six Stealth Black.
How the hell do you
know so much about this?
Everyone knows their
comics, huge in the north.
Blue, whatever I don't care.
Look, don't ever call me that again.
You got that?
I know my stuff.
I was a.
I'm a regular reader of the series.
I rooted for Saru to kick
Jerma's ass time after time.
Well, I hated him, too!
Don't ignore me! Huh?
Whatever you got going
on, it's fishy as hell.
Name yourself.
I am...
Sabo Mask!
That name sucks, and
he's obviously Jerma—oh,
come on, man, was that the best you got?
Why didn't you ask us for help, bro?
Are you joking?
What kind of name is Sober Mask?
But
he was just here—where did he go?
he go
What?
How is he floating like that?
Check it out. Whoa.
I knew it when I saw it.
No doubt about it.
That's Germatech.
His shoes, especially.
It's how they hover around.
That's their trademark.
Show us what you can do!
I said you could beat
me by playing dress-up!
Let's go.
Give me the here.
You really whooped her.
You sure like pissing me
off, don't you, little pest?
How's this happening?
What the heck?
I think he's blocking his claws somehow.
That's the power of
Germa Double Six's cape.
They can form a rock-solid barrier.
That may have worked once,
but I won't fall for it again.
That looks bad.
Stealth Black has a signature
move for times like this.
But can he do it?
No more running!
He vanished!
What the hell?
People don't just disappear like that!
Where'd he go?
Show yourself!
Looks like he pulled it off.
I can't even see him!
Is he moving that fast?
Not quite.
It's Stealth Black's special ability.
He's able to become invisible.
His suit projects an image of his
surroundings over his entire body.
Even Saru, warrior of the sea,
had a hard time with this.
Chairman really is the worst.
Just whose side are you on, anyway?
Also law you sound like a nerd I said
everyone from the north blue nose
What's up with this suit did I disappear
It's almost like the clear clear fruit
Ever since I was little I
dreamed of becoming invisible
power i want but i
watched that wish crumble
before my eyes you thief
you took nami and then
you stole my dream away
from me what the hell
are you talking about
we've never even met before
you messed up i've always
wanted the skill of
invisibility but you had
to find the clear clear
fruit first you took
its powers and you stole
my wish along with it
what that's why he's mad i
thought my dream was dead
now i come to find out
it's possible with Germa
technology of all things
irony's a bitch this
power will be quite useful
think how easy it'll be
to sneak into the Ladies,
I mean how much I'll be able to
help out all of my friends boy.
What a dilemma
An invisible superhero.
Something's going on here?
You're not just some cook who
the hell are you in this form?
You'll have a harder
time hitting me, yeah?
You can zip around fast, who cares?
I was planning to torture
you, nice and slow,
but I suppose that I'd better
kill you quickly instead.
Jaggy, you awake?
Get up!
You got some extra dumplings for me?
I'll repay you, so hand over what you got!
I know you're holding out on me, Jaggy!
This room is ancient, quite curious.
A land isolated for centuries.
These are the people
who created poneglyphs.
Surely there's one here.
Perhaps there's a secret door somewhere
Are you looking for something, madam?
I couldn't hear him at all Who is this?
Go! Go!
Komurasaki It's your turn Show me what
you can do If that is what you desire,
my lord.
Otama, let's make this a
fair and friendly fight!
You got it, Chapul Ramen! I'm ready!
Nope leaves Jutsu!
Ha! Nope!
Oh, zigzag, run!
I'll never become a
bewitchy ninja at this rate.
I'm so poof.
Job, well done.
I had a hard time dodging it all.
Well done, Mewtwo.
I keep thinking about Big Bro.
I sure hope he's okay.
You don't have to worry.
Luffy will always come out on top.
However, Raizo's correspondence
is alarmantly tardy.
I'm a bit concerned.
My master told me something
that worried me, too.
He said no one's ever come
back from the prison in Udon.
Trust me, he'll be fine.
Nin, nin.
Focus on improving yourselves.
That's all we can do.
Nin pose, tree climbing jiu-jitsu.
Nin, nin, nin.
I wish I were strong.
I would simply retrieve
him myself right now.
Nin, nin, nin.
Oh.
There's something washed up on the beach.
Hmm...
mean mean!
She's so skilled!
Though I wonder what the story
is behind that mask of hers.
She wears it every time
she plays the shamisen.
Yes, yes, that's the stuff!
Now this is beautiful!
I love it!
We have you surrounded.
You should consider your actions
in the presence of ninjas.
How bold!
It's possible that she's
never heard of ninjas before.
She could be a foreigner.
Good evening, Ms. Geisha.
Getting into trouble, I see.
I shall hear your explanation.
Speak carefully.
You've only one chance.
This won't be easy after all.
Ancient Zoans are pretty tough.
However, it's gonna take more
than that to defeat Stealth Black.
back.
That stung a bit, but this
suit's pretty durable.
The capital's gonna fall apart before
I do.
Let's go back!
Why are we leaving Sangoro behind?
Because he gave us the okay to move
on.
Yeah, but he was just being cool.
Time to wrap this up and bring
his lifeless buddy to Kyoshiro.
Still, I wonder who he really is.
That's going to attract more
attention and likely more enemies too.
Let's head
Back to Ebisu Town.
Better stay out of the capital a while.
Shooting star, Soma King!
Nearly left a scratch.
Where are you?
Stop hiding!
Supermask!
Reveal yourself now!
Guess I could get used to this name.
I'll have to ask for Nosuke and
Usahachi for a redesign, though.
What do you think it is, Chobo-rimon?
Huh?
Is that a person?
They're colossal, if so.
But not quite giant size.
Wow.
It looks like they might
even be bigger than Kaido.
Is that a woman?
My goodness.
It can't be!
What the heck's being mu -
Is there something wrong? Pshhh!
Keep it down or else
you'll wake her up! Run!
If she sees us, we're done for!
Huh?
No, forget it!
Even if we did run, she'd chase
us all the way to hell and back!
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Do you mean to say you
know who this woman is?
Of course!
Everyone knows her!
The infamous big bomb lies before me!
Lower your voice!
So, who is Big Mom?
I'll explain everything later.
I can't hold back.
I must kill her right now.
I know she's asleep, but
think of her as a Kaido.
She's just as dangerous as him.
It's all over!
Let's go!
What?
Where am I?
What is this?
Who am I?
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?